golfballsdirect.com 2017-06-06

# Terms: Privacy | GolfBallsDirect.com

**Privacy Policy**

Shipping

All APO/FPO orders must use United States Postal Service ONLY as UPS will not deliver to APO/FPO addresses. All orders using FedEX Service must provide a valid physical address as FedEX does NOT deliver to Post Office Boxes. All orders are shipped the next regular business day. In the unlikely event this is not possible the purchaser will be contacted at the email/phone number provided during purchase with further details and options immediately. 

Phone Support - Monday-Friday 8:00 - 4:00 (est)  
Toll  Free @ 866.842.3325  Local @ 772.204.0646  
Email support  \- 24/7  
Shipping or problems with orders: [support@golfballsdirect.com](mailto:support@golfballsdirect.com)  
Mail: Golf Balls Direct - 4490 SE Cheri Court, Stuart, FL  34997

Domestic Shipping

GolfBallsDirect.com ships to the lower 48 states via UPS (or for Hawaii and Puerto Rico via either the USPS or FedEX as available).   
  
International Shipping

Please contact us at [support@golfballsdirect.com](mailto:support@golfballsdirect.com) and provide us with the product you are interested in, the quantity, and your complete shipping address.  We will contact you with a shipping quote and to take your order.  The following are the countries we will ship to. 

Australia | Hong Kong | Saipan  
---|---|---  
Austria | Iceland | Scotland  
Bahamas | Isreal | South Korea  
Belgium | Italy | Spain  
Bermuda | Japan | St. Barthelemy  
British Virgin Islands | Liechtenstein | St. Christopher  
Canada  
| Luxembourg | St. Croix  
Cayman Islands | Madagascar | St. Eustatius  
Channel Islands | Malta | St. John  
China | Mexico | St.Kitts & Nevis  
Cook Islands | Monaco | St. Lucia  
Denmark | Monserrat | St. Maarten  
England | Netherlands | St. Martin  
Fiji | New Caledonia | St. Thomas  
Finland | New Zealand | St. Vincent and Grenadine  
France | Norfolk Island | Sweden  
Germany | Northern Ireland | Switzerland  
Gibraltar | Norway | Tahiti  
Greece | Peoples Rep. of China | United Kingdom  
Greenland | Puerto Rico | US Virgin Island  
Guam | Republic of Ireland | Vatican City State  
Hollnad | Rota | Wales  
  
Expected Shipping Times

It has been our experience that inclement weather and the homeland security alert level (particularly for packages traveling by plane, e.g. to Califonia) can and do influence travel times. We're internet shoppers ourselves and always appreciate fast service... in turn we work hard to provide the same for all our customers. Should your order encounter any delays we do apologize and thank you for your patience, understanding, and cooperation. Your questions are welcome and you may use our Live Chat (in the upper left navigation area) or call us toll free Monday through Friday from 9 am to 4 pm Eastern Standard Time. 

If you need faster deliver and you would like to see a shipping estimate prior to beginning your checkout, you may do so by following these four easy steps: 

  * 1\. Add the item(s) you would like a shipping estimate for to your shopping cart. 
  * 2\. Proceed to checkout. 
  * 3\. Enter your state / zip code information in the total box and click 'Recalculate'. 
  * 4\. Choose a shipping shipping timeframe from the drop down menu labeled 'PLEASE SELECT' (after selecting a carrier from the carrier drop down box above).   

Your shipping rates will be displayed. 

Please note: For FedEX, a business day does not include Saturdays,Sundays, or holidays.

Example: You order golf balls on Monday that take 2 business days to arrive according to the map above. You do not count the day the order was placed as a business day, so your package would arrive on Wednesday, the second business day after the ship date. order.

What information do we collect?

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. 
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 
  * We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. 
  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 
  * To quickly process your transactions. 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 
  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.  
Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include GolfBallsDirect.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

Third party links

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).  

Changes to our policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on August 6, 2003.  

Questions and feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.  
Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.  
Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
